https://leadman.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
At Leadman Electronics, we respect your privacy. Please read below for our complete privacy policy details. By accessing or using the Leadman Electronics Web site, you are accepting the terms of the Leadman Electronics Privacy Policy. Leadman Electronics reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Privacy Policy at the time of such use.
Order Processing
We require your name, company name, A/P contact person, billing address, phone number, email address, shipping address, reseller certificate, Fed tax ID and credit card information to process order. If any questions arise about your order, we will contact you. In general, we will try to contact you by email and if that fails, we will try to contact you by phone. We will not share your account information to any third parties, unless it is absolutely necessary, such as financial institutions, banks or carriers regarding your order processing.
Third Party Privacy
We may include links on our web site to other companies’ sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and content of those sites.
Change Order and Contact Information
To make any changes to your account information and order, please contact us via email or phone and we will be happy to assist you.
Conditions of Use, Notices and Revision
While visiting Leadman Electronics , your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms and Conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of California. Due to the policy might change from time to time, you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
